<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Showcase Template</title><link>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/</link><description>Recent content on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/juan-david-solano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/juan-david-solano/</guid><description>Juan David Solano # About me # I am a sentient being who places a particularly high value on this quality. I am interested in living and creating valuable experiences for myself and other sentient or thinking beings. I am passionate about the movement of the human body, temporal, spatial and conceptual structures. I cultivate mushrooms, practice parkour, make music, write poetry and aphorisms, and try to educate myself as a scientist.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/marcos-macias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/marcos-macias/</guid><description>Marcos Macías # About me # I am 26 years old. I enjoy watching movies and series to relax, nothing too complex or difficult to digest at the moment. I also like to play video games, although I am not an expert and do not know much diversity of them. I like to listen to music and dream of traveling to other countries to experience different parts of the world.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/paula-cadena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Computacion-Visual-2023.github.io/showcase/docs/shortcodes/Members/paula-cadena/</guid><description>Paula Alejandra Cadena Espitia # About me # I am Alejandra, I have always preferred my second name, it feels less serious than &amp;ldquo;Paula&amp;rdquo;, I have always felt at home on the computer, my safe place if you will, which is how I ended up here, I read a lot of sci-fi and fantasy, I love ttrpgs they are my main creative outlet and I hope to use my technical knowledge to help my favorite hobby become even more accessible to everyone.</description></item></channel></rss>